// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the name of the little girl in this story?",
    answer: "Busi",
    options: [
      "Buhle",
      "Grace",
      "Marcia",
      "Busi"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What did Busi want to become when she grows up?",
    answer: "A fashion designer",
    options: [
      "A doctor",
      "A police officer",
      "A fashion designer",
      "A Nurse"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What do fashion designers do?",
    answer: "They design or make clothing and garmets",
    options: [
      "They treat sick people",
      "They deal with criminals",
      "They cook delicious food",
      "They design or make clothing and garmets"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Why did Busi's siblings call her the fashion police?",
    answer: "Because she always kept an eye on their style",
    options: [
      "Because she always kept an eye on their style",
      "Because she always told them about jail",
      "Because she wanted to become a police officer",
      "Because she always kept telling them about crime"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Did Busi's parents promote her dreams?",
    answer: "Yes all the time",
    options: [
      "No they ignored her",
      "Yes all the time",
      "They told her it was not good enough for her",
      "They hated her dreams"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Are dreams important in our lives when growing up?",
    answer: "Yes they are",
    options: [
      "No they are not",
      "They waste our time",
      "Yes they are",
      "No they are just fantasies"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Why are dreams so important?",
    answer: "Dreams motivate us to live a healthy, happy and a life of adventure",
    options: [
      "Dreams will mislead you",
      "Dreams disturbs us from what is important now",
      "Dreams waste our time",
      "Dreams motivate us to live a healthy, happy and a life of adventure"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What do you need to do to achieve your dreams and goals?",
    answer: "You need to focus on your school work and also learn new things everyday",
    options: [
      "You need to focus on your school work and also learn new things everyday",
      "You need to focus on watching lots of tv",
      "You need to play a lot with your friends",
      "You need to do bad things and not listen to your teachers"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Do you think Busi has what it takes to become a fashion designer?",
    answer: "Yes, because she loves fashion and knows how to design and make clothes",
    options: [
      "No, because she does not love fashion and can not make any clothes",
      "Yes, because she loves fashion and knows how to design and make clothes",
      "No, because she hates fashion",
      "No, because she is bad at making fashionable clothes"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Did Busi's dream come true?",
    answer: "Yes it did come true!",
    options: [
      "No but she tried",
      "No she was not good enough",
      "No she failed",
      "Yes it did come true!"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....
  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];
